http://falconefestival.org/index.php/about-us/privacy-policy

Leonard Falcone
International Euphonium and Tuba Festival
HomeAbout UsAbout Dr. FalconeMemories of Leonard FalconeMSU LegacyMSU ArchivesSpartan Marching Band TributeFarewell to BerylPhoto displayEarly HistoryVideo InterviewFestival ObjectivesStatement regarding Diversity, Inclusion & Social JusticeFestival AwardsBoard of DirectorsPrivacy PolicyFestival & CompetitionThe FestivalDaily EventsAdjudicator PanelsThe CompetitionCompetition Overview and Competitor InformationEuphonium Artist InformationTuba Artist InformationEuphonium Student InformationTuba Student Information2021 Required MusicFAQs (pdf link)What to ExpectHistoryCovid-19 and the 2020 Virtual FestivalJourney to the 2020 VIRTUAL FestivalMaster Repertoire ListCommissioned WorksPrevious WinnersPrevious Guest ArtistsPrevious AdjudicatorsPrevious Festival CompetitorsSpecial Medallion RecipientsSolo Works Competition2020 Call for Solo WorksArchives-MSUSupportYOU can support the FestivalFestival EndowmentOur Advertisers2020 Festival DonorsSpecial ThanksStoreContact UsContact EmailsGetting to the FestivalMap of Blue Lake Fine Arts Camp Campus
Login
About Us
About Dr. FalconeFarewell to BerylEarly HistoryFestival ObjectivesStatement regarding Diversity, Inclusion & Social JusticeFestival AwardsBoard of DirectorsPrivacy Policy
FalconeFestival.org Privacy Policy
Information Collected and Stored Automatically
When you visit falconefestival.org, it is hosted by Bluehost, which collects Log Data to which we have access. Falcone Festival may store some or all of the following Log Data: your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, the Internet address from which you access falconefestival.org, the Internet address of the website from which you linked to falconefestival.org, the browser and operating system used, the date and time of your visit, the pages of our site that you visit, the items clicked on a page, and other statistics.
This information is used to measure the number of visitors to the various sections of our site, analyze patterns of usage, and to make the site more useful. This information is not used for associating patterns of site navigation with individual users.
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties any personally identifiable information.
To view the Bluehost privacy policy, go to https://www.bluehost.com/terms/privacy-policy.
Third Party Links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include links to third party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Falcone Festival Competition Registrants
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in conducting our registration process so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.
Download a pdf file of the Privacy Policy
Policy adopted at Falcone Festival Board Meeting August 12, 2017
2021 FESTIVAL DEADLINESMarch 31...Application DeadlineEarly May...Semi-Finalists NotifiedAugust 6-9...Festival Competition
Privacy Policy
Festival Statement regarding Diversity, Inclusion & Social Justice #BlackLivesMatter
Login
Copyright © 2020 Leonard Falcone International Euphonium and Tuba Festival ®
template Joomla
